freehandmusic.com 2008-12-21

# Download Digital Sheet Music 24/7 | FreeHandMusic.com

How We Collect Information

The FreeHandMusic site collects personally identifying information when customers:

> 1\. purchase digital music, print music or other products  
>  2\. provide content suggestions or send queries to FreeHandMusic employees  
>  3\. enter drawings, sweepstakes, contests or sign-up for FreeHandMusic's e-mail newsletter

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still visit most of the FreeHandMusic.com site. However, you will not have access to areas and products that require personal identification.

When you register or order online, FreeHandMusic collects your name, mailing address, User IDs, Usernames and passwords.

When you make a purchase using your credit card we pass your credit card number through secure payment gateways for verification and processing. We do not store your credit card number or expiration date.

We respect your right to privacy and have implemented this Privacy Policy in recognition of the importance of using in a responsible way the information you choose to provide us.

How We Use The Information We Collect

We use the information to help us improve our communications with you so you receive more of what you want and less of what you don't want. We send confirmation e-mail to our customers when we receive orders and ship orders. We also provide our customers with a newsletter that introduces new products and provides FreeHandMusic updates.

We use credit card information to process orders; never for marketing purposes.

We use information received from drawings, contests and sweepstakes to administer these promotions. We also use this information to let you know about our products and services.

Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, or unless your prior permission is obtained, FreeHandMusic does not share with third parties personally identifying information collected from the distribution of FreeHandMusic products or gathered on the FreeHandMusic website, except that FreeHandMusic may share such information with third parties who are the developer, owner or licensor of the product or service in question. Finally, we must reserve the right to disclose information if required by law to do so.

Removing Your Name From Our Mailing List

If for any reason you wish to remove your name from the FreeHandMusic mailing list (newsletter), simply:

> 1\. Go to www.FreeHandMusic.com  
>  2\. Log in (if not automatically logged in)  
>  3\. Click My Account  
>  4\. Click Edit My Account on the Account Information page  
>  5\. Un-check the box at the bottom of the page and click the Update Profile button

Or you may notify us:

| 

By telephone:

| 1-800-917-1949  
---|---  
  
By mail:

| Customer Relations  
FreeHand Systems  
95 First Street, Suite 200  
Los Altos, CA 94022  
  
About IP Addresses

FreeHandMusic collects IP addresses to help with its system administration.

An IP (Internet Protocol) address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're connected to the Internet. Web servers – the big computers that "serve" up Web pages – automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

When customers request pages from FreeHandMusic.com, our servers log the customers' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.

Use of "Cookies"

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases and preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is now an industry standard – you'll find them at most major websites.

By showing how and when consumers use the site, cookies help webmasters meet their customers' needs. Many improvements and updates to websites are based on data collected by means of cookies.

FreeHandMusic uses cookies:

  * to distinguish you from others during your visit to our site 
  * to track (with a temporary cookie) which products you've chosen to view and/or purchase while shopping.  
NOTE: If you decline these types of cookies, you may have difficulty ordering your selections.

FreeHandMusic does not use cookies:

  * to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie

Information gathered by means of cookies is never shared with any third parties whatsoever.

Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you whenever cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of a website, like FreeHandMusic's shopping areas, will not function properly if you do so.

Assent

By using the FreeHandMusic website, you signify your assent to the FreeHandMusic Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the FreeHandMusic website following the posting of changes to these terms will signify that you accept the changes.

Contact information

If you have any questions about FreeHandMusic's privacy policy, please send an e-mail to the FreeHandMusic legal department at  http://www.FreeHandMusic.com/Feedback.aspx.
